=The Little Red Matchmaker= =Episode 22=
=Si Kecil Pemadu Cinta= =Episod 22=
You don't remember at all?
Kamu tidak ingat sama sekali?
Qing.
Qing.
Are you there?
Kamu ada di sana?
How about this?
Bagaimana dengan ini?
My favorite snack.
Makanan ringan kegemaran saya.
(Master.)
(Tuan.)
(I will make you remember.)
(Aku akan membuatmu ingat.)
I really can't remember.
Saya betul-betul tidak dapat mengingatnya.
It's okay.
Tidak apa-apa.
You can forget about me.
Anda boleh melupakan saya.
But you can't forget love.
Tetapi anda tidak boleh melupakan cinta.
(Ying)
(Ying)
You finally remembered.
Akhirnya kau ingat.
I didn't.
Aku tidak.
But I've fallen in love with you again.
Tapi aku jatuh cinta padamu lagi.
Master.
Tuan.
After tonight,
Setelah malam ini,
if Jiang Changqing still loves you,
jika Jiang Changqing masih mencintaimu,
the Heartless Curse will be triggered,
Kutukan Tanpa Hati akan terpicu,
and he will die.
dan dia akan mati.
I can save him.
Aku bisa menyelamatkannya.
What do you want?
Apa yang kau inginkan?
Kneel before me.
Berlutut di hadapanku.
Beg me.
Mintalah padaku.
After taking this pill,
Setelah meminum pil ini,
he will forget you.
dia akan melupakanmu.
(Master.)
(Tuan.)
(Love isn't about possession.)
(Cinta bukan tentang kepemilikan.)
(It's about giving)
(Tetapi tentang memberi)
(and sacrificing.)
(dan berkorban.)
(Our love ends here in this life.)
(Cinta kita berakhir di dunia ini.)
♪I have never backed down♪
♪Aku tidak pernah mundur♪
♪Fearless of getting hurt♪
♪Tak takut terluka♪
(This beautiful dream)
(Impian indah ini)
(is the last gift I give you.)
(adalah hadiah terakhir yang kuberikan padamu.)
♪That will be consumed by time♪
♪Yang akan terkikis oleh waktu♪
♪I miss the warmth of you♪
♪Aku merindukan kehangatanmu♪
♪Finding warmth in soft words and tones♪
♪Menemukan kehangatan dalam kata-kata lembut♪
(Forget me.)
(Lupakan aku.)
♪Leaving ashes in the world♪
♪Meninggalkan abu di dunia ini♪
(May you be free of pain)
(Moga engkau bebas dari rasa sakit)
(after the dream.)
(setelah impian ini.)
♪Leaving residual heat chasing after the wind♪
♪Meninggalkan kehangatan sisa mengejar angin♪
♪Memories surround me♪
♪Kenangan mengelilingiku♪
♪I always cherish the fragments of memory♪
♪Aku selalu menghargai fragmen kenangan♪
♪Your breath lingers by my ear♪
♪Nafasmu masih terdengar di telingaku♪
♪The night begins to blur♪
♪Malam mulai kabur♪
♪I fantasize about a kiss at your brow♪
♪Aku membayangkan ciuman di dahimu♪
(Who is she?)
(Siapa dia?)
(Why does my heart ache so much?)
(Mengapa hatiku sangat sakit?)
(It hurts.)
(Sakit.)
(To be continued)
(Akan dilanjutkan)
You're here to ruin my plans again.
Kau datang untuk mengacaukan rencanaku lagi.
Today, you will die.
Hari ini, kau akan mati.
Nine tails unite.
Sembilan ekor bersatu.
♪As the moonlit night is drawing on♪
♪Seperti malam yang diterangi bulan♪
♪A solitary wild goose is flying in the fog♪
♪Seekor angsa liar terbang di dalam kabut♪
♪The waning moon is deep in thought♪
♪Bulan yang semakin suram dalam pemikiran♪
♪Shedding a golden light over the road♪
♪Menyinari jalan dengan cahaya keemasan♪
♪I'm longing for returning home♪
♪Aku merindukan pulang ke rumah♪
♪I abandoned cultivation for a new life♪
♪Aku meninggalkan pertanian untuk kehidupan baru♪
♪And for the beauty in my heart♪
♪Dan untuk keindahan di dalam hatiku♪
♪We meet only in dreams♪
♪Kita hanya bertemu dalam mimpi♪
♪Souls entwine over the time♪
♪Jiwa-jiwa terikat sepanjang waktu♪
♪The shattered fate breaks the bond♪
♪Takdir yang hancur memutuskan ikatan kita♪
♪Years pass by like a dream♪
♪Tahun-tahun berlalu seperti mimpi♪
♪My yearning turns into a melody♪
♪Rinduku berubah menjadi melodi♪
♪You are my eternal love in heart♪
♪Kaulah cinta abadi dalam hatiku♪
♪My past life fades like clouds dispersing♪
♪Kehidupan masa laluku menghilang seperti awan yang berhamburan♪
♪As I meet you in this life♪
♪Saat aku bertemu denganmu dalam kehidupan ini♪
♪A thousand years of waiting is not in vain♪
♪Seribu tahun menunggu tidak sia-sia♪
♪Dreaming in a cool, long night♪
♪Mimpi dalam malam yang sejuk dan panjang♪
♪Who is waiting alone♪
♪Siapa yang menunggu sendirian♪
♪My endless yearning stretches on♪
♪Rindu yang tak berkesudahan terus berlanjut♪
♪Despite the hard fate♪
♪Meski takdir sulit♪
♪I hope to reconnect with you♪
♪Aku berharap bisa bersatu kembali denganmu♪
♪And spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Dan menghabiskan sisa hidupku bersamamu♪